hello and welcome to the third tutorial
on how to program a gript 2 this
tutorial I'm going to show you more
about RC so RC has a lot of buttons okay
this one here let's upload files which I
went over in the last tutorial this is
the player list which I also went over
in the last tutorial this one is the
accounts List It has nothing to do with
programming you could just ignore it
I've never found a use for it the same
with this I've never found a use for it
it just
you can ignore these if you're like me
and just
program
so here is the
options this also is pretty much the
same thing you know it's nothing to do
with programming next to that is server
flx this is very important with
programming this is like data that's on
the server itself we'll go over this
later this is the folder configuration
right there it's like what files hold
what kind of what folders hold what kind
of files you don't really want to mess
with it unless you know what you're
doing this is the server options it's
things like start level uh unstick me
level like what levels they start with
the player starts on when they first
enter like Bush items Badd items things
like that below is the local NPCs you
can just ignore this
one it's same thing like the other
buttons that don't have anything can do
with programming below that is the level
list it does nothing and to the left of
that is these three buttons these are
very important this is the NPCs button
this holds all the scripts for NPCs like
NPCs that are online which is this are
different than the ones that are online
like the one on the level editor and we
upload you know when you uploaded a noob
that's a level NPC this is like an
online NPC online NPCs work a bit
differently they're a lot harder to
manage but they can do things a they do
things a bit differently we'll go over
that later this is the
weapons button it holds all the weapons
like TNT like I mean like this is a
script that I made these kind of
scripts are on the player them like
himself like they could be a HUD in a
corner or they could be the player's
movement like how they
run it's very important this is the
classes button the last button on the RC
this holds things like let's it's really
hard to explain let's say you have a
let's say you have an NPC and you want
it to call and you want it to run this
rock script you want it to run it well
to do that you would just call the Rock
script which is a class you call it and
then this script gets sent over to the
MPC or or a weapon if you want to do it
like that
and that's it for this RC also you if
you press in the bottom left corner
start and click RC or remote control
it'll show you an in-game RC it has
about the same features as the out of
game client or for RC except player list
doesn't
work the scripts buttons are put into
just one big button I mean one big
button and there are two extra buttons
here this you can turn you can type in
like a command line or something it'll
give you help but it's not very helpful
and here's just GUI control you don't
really need to do it or use these two
buttons at least right now so anyway
that's it for this episode uh now you
know how to use RC more and the in-game
RC so uh by bye